Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 514, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Xerox Corporation facilities located in Rochester, New York (Monroe County) and Local 14A the Xerographic Division, Amalgamated Clothing & Textile Workers Union, A.F.L.-C.I.O.: 1992-1995 (Box 514, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Xerox Corporation facilities located in Rochester, New York (Monroe County) and Local 14A the Xerographic Division, Amalgamated Clothing & Textile Workers Union, A.F.L.-C.I.O.: 1992-1995 (Box 514, Folder 3)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 514, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Advance, 1991; Publication (Box 514, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1991:Summer)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 514, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Amalgamated Action, 1973; Publication (Box 514, Folder 5)
    Notes: Apr.-Aug., Oct.-Dec. (1973)
  - Item 2: Amalgamated Action, 1974; Publication (Box 514, Folder 5)
    Notes: Jan.-Mar., May, July-Oct. (1974)
  - Item 3: Amalgamated Action, 1975; Publication (Box 514, Folder 5)
    Notes: Jan.-Feb.-June, Sept.-Dec. (1975)
  - Item 4: Amalgamated Action, 1976; Publication (Box 514, Folder 5)
    Notes: Mar., July-Oct. (1976)
  - Item 5: Amalgamated Action, 1977; Publication (Box 514, Folder 5)
    Notes: Jan. (1977)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 514, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Action, 1982; Publication (Box 514, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1982:Winter)
- CSEA (Civil Service Employees Association), Publication (Box 514, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Advance notice of closing policy CSEA - AFSCME - New York State: an assessment by Felician F. Foltman, 1977; Publication (Box 514, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: CSEA Members' meeting - Wed. Nov. 30, 1994, Publication (Box 514, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Security in the workplace, 1992; Publication (Box 514, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Evolution of a labor union, 1986; Publication (Box 514, Folder 7)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 515, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: National agreement between Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: dated as of October 1, 1987, Publication (Box 515, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: National agreement between Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: dated as of April 1, 1982, Publication (Box 515, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: National agreement between Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: dated as of October 1, 1985, Publication (Box 515, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: National agreement between Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: dated as of October 1, 1990, Publication (Box 515, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: National agreement between Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: dated as of October 1, 1993, Publication (Box 515, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company. Research Department, Publication (Box 515, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Benefits Brief, 1989; Publication (Box 515, Folder 2)
    Notes: Mar., June-July, Oct., Dec. (1989)
  - Item 2: Benefits Brief, 1990; Publication (Box 515, Folder 2)
    Notes: Feb., May, July/Aug., Oct./Nov. (1990)
  - Item 3: Benefits Brief, 1991; Publication (Box 515, Folder 2)
    Notes: Jan./Feb. -May/June, Sept./Oct. (1991)
  - Item 4: Benefits Brief, 1992; Publication (Box 515, Folder 2)
    Notes: Jan./Feb., May/June-Nov./Dec. (1992)
  - Item 5: Benefits Brief, 1993; Publication (Box 515, Folder 2)
    Notes: Apr. Aug. (1993)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1976; Publication (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1978; Publication (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1981; Publication (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1987; Publication (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1990; Publication (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Constitution, 1993; Publication (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Constitution, 1914; Publication (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Membership book and Constitution, 1918; Publication (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Third Constitutional Convention, 1984; Publication (Box 515, Folder 3)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 515, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Ball and chain for African-American workers?, 1994; Publication (Box 515, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: ACTWU and civil rights, Publication (Box 515, Folder 4)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 515, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: flyer - Disability project, Publication (Box 515, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Economic impact of the OSHA cotton dust standard, 1983; Publication (Box 515, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Partners in prevention: health & safety acton manual for local unions, 1991; Publication (Box 515, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The right-to-know guide: our legal rights to workplace health & safety information, 1992; Publication (Box 515, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Workers' compensation: a union responsibility, Publication (Box 515, Folder 5)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 515, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Fiber facts - Nov. 1980 -- vol. 2, no. 4, Publication (Box 515, Folder 6)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 515, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: flyers - What is the AHAP?; Amalgamated Life's Health Care Network; Opt-Out program; Medical certification program; Mail Service Prescription drug program, Publication (Box 515, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Summary plan description of the Health and Welfare Plan: the Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1993; Publication (Box 515, Folder 7)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 515, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Brand name directory (4th ed.), 1989; Publication (Box 515, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Brand name directory: of products made by ACTWU members, Publication (Box 515, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Brand name directory (3rd ed), 1986; Publication (Box 515, Folder 8)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 515, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Labor Leadership - Mar., Aug., Dec. (1988); Mar., July, Nov. (1989); Oct. (1990); Jan., July, Dec. (1991); June (1992); Feb. (1993), 1988-1993 (Box 515, Folder 9)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 515, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Agreement and plan of merger and consolidation, 1976; Publication (Box 515, Folder 10)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 516, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Amalgamated Retired Members Newsletter, 1973; Publication (Box 516, Folder 1)
    Notes: May- Dec. (1973)
  - Item 2: Amalgamated Retired Members Newsletter, 1974; Publication (Box 516, Folder 1)
    Notes: Jan.- Oct., Dec. (1974)
  - Item 3: Amalgamated Retired Members Newsletter, 1975; Publication (Box 516, Folder 1)
    Notes: Jan.- Mar., May-Aug., Oct.-Dec. (1975)
  - Item 4: Amalgamated Retired Members Newsletter, 1976; Publication (Box 516, Folder 1)
    Notes: Jan.- May, July, Oct.-Dec. (1976)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 516, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Office Newsletter, 1976; Publication (Box 516, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1976)
  - Item 2: Office Unity, 1979; Publication (Box 516, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no2-6 (1979)
  - Item 3: Office Unity, 1980; Publication (Box 516, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.1-6, 10-11 (1980)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 516, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: News for Older New Yorkers, 1977-1978 (Box 516, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.3-4 (1977/1978)
  - Item 2: News for Older New Yorkers, 1978; Publication (Box 516, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.1-4 (1978)
  - Item 3: News for Older New Yorkers, 1979; Publication (Box 516, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4no.1 (1979)
  - Item 4: Network News, 1978; Publication (Box 516, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1978)
  - Item 5: News for New Jersey ACTWU Retired Members, 1978; Publication (Box 516, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1978)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union), Publication (Box 516, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Amalgamated News: Philadelphia Joint Board, 1978; Publication (Box 516, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.25 (1978)
  - Item 2: ACTWU News: J.P. Stevens antes up $31,445, 1980; Publication (Box 516, Folder 4)
    Notes: Press Release
  - Item 3: ACTWU News: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers sign National settlement with J.P. Stevens Co.: foresee 'harmonious, productive relationship', 1980; Publication (Box 516, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: ACTWU News: Substantial pay and benefit hikes won be Clothing and Textile Union for Metro Area Dye, Print Workers, 1980; Publication (Box 516, Folder 4)
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Publication (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1987; Publication (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: 1982-84 Municipal coalition economic agreement, 1982-1984 (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Agreement - March 1974, Publication (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Agreement - 1973-1974 (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Independent Heavy and Highway Agreement, 1985-1988 (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Agreement, 1986; Publication (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Agreement, 1973; Publication (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Agreement with the Carpenters District Council of Westchester County, N.Y. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America and the Building Trades Employers Association of Westchester and Putnam Counties, N.Y. Inc. and the Builders Institute of We, 1973; Publication (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Millwright and Piledriver agreement between Carpenters' District Council of Rochester and Vicinity: Millwright and Piledriver Local Union NO. 1163 and the Construction Employers Labor Relations Association of New York State, Inc.: May 1, 1973 to May 31, 1, 1974; Publication (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Agreement between Carpenters' District Council of Rochester and Vicinity and the Construction Employers Labor Relations Association of New York State, Inc.: May 1, 1973 to May 31, 1974, Publication (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Agreement between Employers engaged in shipbuilding & repair, boatbuilding & repair & allied industries and the Pacific Coast Marine Carpenters Council of Washington, Oregon and California: b July 1, 1974 - June 30, 1977, Publication (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Agreement with the Carpenters District Council of Westchester County, N.Y. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America and the Building Trades Employers Association of Westchester and Putnam Counties, N.Y. Inc. and the Builders Institute of We, 1973; Publication (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Agreement with the Carpenters District Council of Westchester County, N.Y. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Publication (Box 516, Folder 5)
- Major League Baseball Players Association, Publication (Box 516, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Average salaries in Major League Baseball: 1967-1994 (Box 516, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Major league baseball players benefit plan, 1990-1992 (Box 516, Folder 6)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 516, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: News UAW, 1988; Publication (Box 516, Folder 7)
    Notes: September 20, 1988.
  - Item 2: News UAW, 1990; Publication (Box 516, Folder 7)
    Notes: January 15, 1990.
  - Item 3: UAW Local 2300 has recently filed grievances on behalf of three video Ithaca employees who have been arbitrarily disciplined or fired., 1993; Publication (Box 516, Folder 7)
    Author: Local 2300
  - Item 4: Labor Alert! - An appeal from the Tompkins/Cortland Labor Coalition for Community and Labor Solidarity, 1993; Publication (Box 516, Folder 7)
- Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers International Union, Publication (Box 516, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1986; Publication (Box 516, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1990; Publication (Box 516, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1994; Publication (Box 516, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Brown & Williamson Tobacco Corporation and Local Union Number 187-T: 1980-1983 (Box 516, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Brown & Williamson Tobacco Corporation and Local Union Number 185-T: 1980-1983 (Box 516, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Agreement between The Kroger Co. and the Bakery, ConfectioneryLocal 372-A [this is a copy of the agreement, and has no 'official' title page of sorts, so wasn't cataloged], 1993; Publication (Box 516, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Agreement between NABISCO and the Bakery, ConfectioneryLocal 300, 1977-1979 (Box 516, Folder 8)
    Notes: Very bad copy.
- Oregon AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 516, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Reports, 1980; Publication (Box 516, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.22:no.1-9, 11 (1980)
- AFL-CIO. New York City Central Labor Council, Publication (Box 516, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Labor News, 1986; Publication (Box 516, Folder 10)
    Notes: May, July, Dec. (1986)
  - Item 2: Labor News, 1987; Publication (Box 516, Folder 10)
    Notes: Apr., Nov. (1987)
  - Item 3: Labor News, 1988; Publication (Box 516, Folder 10)
    Notes: May,-July, Mar., Aug.-Sept., Nov. (1988)
  - Item 4: Labor News, 1989; Publication (Box 516, Folder 10)
    Notes: Feb.-Mar., May, Aug.-Oct., Dec. (1989)
  - Item 5: Labor News, 1990; Publication (Box 516, Folder 10)
    Notes: Jan., Mar.-Aug., Oct.-Nov. (1990)
  - Item 6: Labor News, 1991; Publication (Box 516, Folder 10)
    Notes: Feb., May-Nov. (1991)
  - Item 7: Labor News, 1992; Publication (Box 516, Folder 10)
    Notes: Jan.-May, July-Aug., Oct., Dec. (1992)
  - Item 8: How unions help your family: important facts they won't tell you in your newspaper or on radio and TV, 1986; Publication (Box 516, Folder 10)
- New York State AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 516, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: 51st Convention renewed its pledges to conduct an advanced campaign to win support for state, county and city purchasing of Union made goods and services, 1978; Publication (Box 516, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Twenty-sixth Constitutional Convention, 1990; Publication (Box 516, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Working together, 1985; Publication (Box 516, Folder 11)
    Author: Edward J. Cleary
    Notes: Article published in the Legislative Gazette, Dec. 9, 1985
- AFL-CIO. Massachusetts State Labor Council, Publication (Box 516, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Massachusetts Labor Leader, 1984; Publication (Box 516, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 1-3, 6-7 (1984)
  - Item 2: Massachusetts Labor Leader, 1985; Publication (Box 516, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 1, 4-7 (1985)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 517, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: ACTWU bargaining units, by Joint Boad and Directly-Affiliated Locals -- Research Dept., ACTWU - Mar. 30, 1993, Publication (Box 517, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: ACTWU bargaining unit directory - May 1995, Publication (Box 517, Folder 1)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 517, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Facts for bargaining: cotton garment: February 1990, Publication (Box 517, Folder 2)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 517, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: ACTWU bargaining unit directory - June 1991, Publication (Box 517, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Contingent workers in ACTWU shops and ACTWU contracts, 1990; Publication (Box 517, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Contingent workers in ACTWU shops and ACTWU contracts, 1990; Publication (Box 517, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Bargaining on women's issues and family concerns: clauses from ACTWU contracts, 1990; Publication (Box 517, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Bargaining on women's issues and family concerns: clauses from ACTWU contracts, 1990; Publication (Box 517, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Bargaining on technology: a compilation of ACTWU and other union contract clauses and related materials, 1992; Publication (Box 517, Folder 3)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 517, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Selected bibliography of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1980; Publication (Box 517, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: ACTWU bargaining unit directory - June 1989, Publication (Box 517, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Selected bibliography of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1987; Publication (Box 517, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Selected bibliography of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1987; Publication (Box 517, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Bargaining on women's issues and family concerns: clauses from ACTWU contracts, 1988; Publication (Box 517, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Bargaining on women's issues and family concerns: clauses from ACTWU contracts, 1988; Publication (Box 517, Folder 4)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Amalgamated Retired Members Newsletter - Jan.-Mar. (1977), Publication (Box 518, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: ACTWU Retirees Newsletter, 1977; Publication (Box 518, Folder 1)
    Notes: Apr.-May, Aug.-Sept. (1977)
  - Item 3: Seniority, 1977; Publication (Box 518, Folder 1)
    Notes: Oct.-Dec. (1977)
  - Item 4: Seniority, 1978; Publication (Box 518, Folder 1)
    Notes: Jan.-Oct., Dec. (1978)
  - Item 5: Seniority, 1979; Publication (Box 518, Folder 1)
    Notes: Jan.-Mar., May-Oct. (1979)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Seniority, 1980; Publication (Box 518, Folder 2)
    Notes: Jan.-Dec. (1980)
  - Item 2: Seniority, 1981; Publication (Box 518, Folder 2)
    Notes: Feb.-Mar., May-June, Aug.-Dec. (1981)
  - Item 3: Seniority, 1982; Publication (Box 518, Folder 2)
    Notes: Jan., Nov. (1982)
  - Item 4: Seniority, 1983; Publication (Box 518, Folder 2)
    Notes: July-Aug. (1983)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Social Justice, 1978-1980 (Box 518, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.18-28 (1978-1980)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Project abstract, Publication (Box 518, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: ACTWU News - For immediate release - NLRB charges Brooks Brothers with illegal firings, other law violations at NJ Plant, 1979; Publication (Box 518, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: A guide for labor's involvement with handicapped individuals, 1979; Publication (Box 518, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Job analysis and accommodation manual for the male apparel industry, 1979; Publication (Box 518, Folder 4)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Southwest Progress - Fall, Winter (1989), Publication (Box 518, Folder 5)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Staff News Letter, 1970; Publication (Box 518, Folder 6)
    Notes: Oct.-Nov. (1970)
  - Item 2: Staff News Letter, 1971; Publication (Box 518, Folder 6)
    Notes: Jan.- July, Sept.-Dec. (1971)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Staff News Letter, 1972; Publication (Box 518, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan., Feb., May, Dec. (1972)
  - Item 2: Staff News Letter, 1973; Publication (Box 518, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan., May-June, Nov.-Dec. (1973)
  - Item 3: May Staff Newsletter - Labor and the new economic program, 1972; Publication (Box 518, Folder 7)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Staff News Letter, 1974; Publication (Box 518, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.-Mar., May-June (1974)
  - Item 2: Staff News Letter, 1976; Publication (Box 518, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan. (1976)
  - Item 3: Staff News Letter, 1976; Publication (Box 518, Folder 8)
    Notes: Spring 1976
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: J.P. Stevens and the law, Publication (Box 518, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: J.P. Stevens and Occupational Safety and Health, Publication (Box 518, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: J.P. Stevens: the company, Publication (Box 518, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: J.P. Stevens and the National Labor Relations Law, Publication (Box 518, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: J.P. Stevens and the impoverishment of the Carolinas, Publication (Box 518, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: J.P. Stevens has pursued a runaway shop policy, stranding thousands of Northern workers in closed plants, Publication (Box 518, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: J.P. Stevens and its record of discrimination in employment practices, Publication (Box 518, Folder 9)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: 21 month strike at Farah ends with recognition of Amalgamated, 1974; Publication (Box 518, Folder 10)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Talking Union - Apr. 1984, Publication (Box 518, Folder 11)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Threads, Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.1
  - Item 2: Threads, Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.2
  - Item 3: Threads, Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.3
  - Item 4: Threads, Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.4
  - Item 5: Threads, 1979; Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.5 (1979)
  - Item 6: Threads, 1979; Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.1:no.6 (1979:Apr.)
  - Item 7: Threads, 1979; Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.1:no.7 (1979:May)
  - Item 8: Threads, 1979; Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1979:June/July)
  - Item 9: Threads, 1979; Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1979:Aug./Sep.)
  - Item 10: Threads, 1979; Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1979:Oct./Nov.)
  - Item 11: Threads, 1979-1980 (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1979/1980: Winter)
  - Item 12: Threads, 1980; Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1980:Spring)
  - Item 13: Threads, 1980; Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1980:Summer)
  - Item 14: Threads, 1980; Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1980/1981:Fall/Winter)
  - Item 15: Threads! Program Guide, Publication (Box 518, Folder 12)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: ACTWU Union Privilege Programs -, 1995; Publication (Box 518, Folder 13)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: VOICE, 1977; Publication (Box 518, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.4:no. (1977)
  - Item 2: VOICE, 1978; Publication (Box 518, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.5:no.1-4 (1978)
  - Item 3: VOICE, 1979; Publication (Box 518, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.6:no.1-4 (1979)
  - Item 4: VOICE, 1980; Publication (Box 518, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.7:no.2-3 (1980)
  - Item 5: VOICE, 1981; Publication (Box 518, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.8:no.1-2 (1981)
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 518, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Las grandes corporaciones las grandes influencias y los intereses creados controlan el pais., Publication (Box 518, Folder 15)